let's go peace okay it's been a while
since we've done a trash-talking
periscope so I think it's about time we
are gonna watch the Ashley Vance
zooks profile so you guys know
I felt kama get a start and now okay so
first first first first we break down
this tagline your robot taxi has arrived
kind of no it hasn't
show me where I can buy a Zuke's can I
buy a Zook somewhere no I can't buy a
zooms anywhere so justjust just to make
this this clear um now let's start with
this well you can see it better let's go
over to youtube so you can see it better
right that's a personal bicycle oh look
it's a guy thing okay um so a few
interesting things about zooks you can
actually see their GPS module so this is
their ladder that they're using um this
is a Bella dine puck right so to compare
way mo2 zooks this is this is this isn't
off-the-shelf turbid since on Tesla's
board that's great
why don't any funds oops don't funds
oops um Susan LM Park this is the the
lighter that they're using again it's an
off-the-shelf lidar it's fairly cheap oh
by now can actually buy something from
valid I know I can uh please tell us a
little about yourself and then they'll
be in touch okay all right please put
your lighters on Amazon thank you okay
so they also show you the inertial
system that they're using
I got the video slowed down and running
in a real slow mode so they show you
that a shot of it it's a no XTS system
it's that um so they're using an
off-the-shelf inertial localizer and
this is this is like a GPS so you see
primary and secondary those are your two
GPS antennas so this is very similar to
a plan X we can look and they're
probably using the same stuff on their
on their Lexus Rx's um this is just
another one this is actually the one
that happens to also be used on the
data set so interesting thing about
about success sensors there
off-the-shelf things um so the first
part of this video entry on camera using
the first part of this video they show
you these things and now why exactly
zukes is building these things it kind
of makes no sense by the way guys face
to be to me to tell you why I'm doing
this
I don't do this about weigh my right I
don't do this about lame-o like lame-o
might be a good investment lame-o might
be a good company I think there PR is
extremely distasteful but you know okay
what's the problem with lame-o no
problems the problem with zooks
is they increase hype to a point that it
isn't true um and we'll get to what
isn't true
and there's no way to really know so
it's really hard to talk about the
quality of a self-driving car drive um
one of the metrics that can be used is
disengagement so then if you go in this
video they talked about you know what's
actually going on in the zukes car and
they go for a drive back to the office
in San Francisco it's like a 20 minute
drive mostly freeway um
notice let's let's freeze the frame
right here what don't you see scobie's
it's interactive you gotta talk what's
not in this picture and it's very
deliberately framed this way scroll for
old comments what's what's missing from
this picture that you might see in any
other car a steering wheel right so
notice the way that this shot is frames
so Wow look Suk's has a car without a
steering wheel right and that's what you
think if you're just glancing over this
video but that's the backseat of the car
guess what's in the front seat of the
car and we'll get a shot of them in a
minute look at you didn't see that guy
anywhere else look at that guy who says
how come we didn't get introduced right
so the video unfortunately is not really
an unedited um unedited thing oh we can
go over here to this is this is a video
that Cruz Automation released and it
actually is an unedited video of a drive
throughout City to San Francisco um and
they show you look here's the safety
driver here's the safety driver you know
with their hands a safe distance from
the wheel but not touching it okay they
have a little gimmicky thing that says
autonomous but this is a real video this
is an impressive technology demo um this
is hype right and you know what car a
guy we do love hype now
you guys man look at the symmetry of the
yeah I wouldn't mind a chauffeur either
what are they cost I'm okay so you know
if he hears it cut across the things
tracking the trough that's all great um
so the only thing that I could really
nitpick do you guys remember the drive
that AI video the line following robot
that that one was bad
um this was the only thing that I could
really nitpick that I think is probably
a disengagement right they don't tell
you whether there were disengagement syn
the drive mean again they're sitting in
the backseat you can't tell whether that
driver is casually pressing on the brake
pedal touching the steering wheel a
little bit I can do the same demo with
open pilot you know magicians do this
all the time you got the guy in the back
seat to distract the guy who you doing
the trick for you put the guy in the
front seat who's actually like stuff in
the rabbit in the Hat when nobody's
looking
look I'm not saying this is true I'm
just saying it could be true we're all
having fun here believe this one look at
this one okay so here's a car here's a
vehicle right I want you to watch I'm
gonna slow this down the maximum I can
we're going down to 0.25 speed all right
I'm one of those conspiracy guys on
YouTube now take a look at when it
breaks right as a human when would you
hit the brakes right the brakes are hit
right there
well after obviously that car is is in
your path right now I can't tell for
sure or not whether this was a
disengagement but this is not what a
human driver would this looks to me like
they were expecting the autonomous
system to break the autonomous system
didn't break what you could probably
really do is if you take this video
frame by frame you could see exactly
like what the braking look at this look
at this you could see exactly what the
braking trajectory was like right and
then it starts to break hard here at the
last minute you can see the buck forward
oh you know what you know what wait wait
let's do a quick bonus video of Pony AI
Oh Pony AI is my favorite
okay so Pony AI is using a Lincoln MKZ
um ah
this part of the scene okay so this part
of the scene for the Pony AI you can see
there they have the sorry sorry sorry we
got a little distracted of Zeus why
would you do this for a minute because I
found this video really funny so here we
go they're gonna look at this cyclist
here watch the steering wheel
look how it jerked like that that is not
a self-driving car that is a human in
the backseat with an Xbox controller
like this isn't off-the-shelf demo car
so this is worse than Zeus okay this is
worse than Zeus
there's things out there worse than Zeus
let's not say Zeus is the walkway oh
wait you want to you want to watch the
wheel get jerked by the Xbox controller
guy again let's let's really go to it
we'll go to point 5 speed here alright
now to be fair the car was probably
autonomous up until that point and it
probably did autonomously brake for the
biker and then in order to make it seem
smooth look look look look look so this
is right when the human jerks the wheel
that's clearly an Xbox controller
maneuver oh we're gonna hit something
good heads up jerk the wheel right come
on pony aaaah you can do better
um no yeah you wanna what you want to
watch the collision you guys wanna watch
the phantom AI collision uh-huh but yeah
so this is all I could really nitpick
from the zukes video to be fair it's not
too bad I just wish they'd wear it like
so big with the hype do you talk about
your diss engagements openly and
publicly by the way I'm the highway
Carly I had zero but that doesn't matter
it doesn't matter because what matters
is hype so now on we're pivoting the
full hype got a pivot to hide bro oh so
let's see what else we can pick out of
the nukes video
now honestly if this was all that Zook
showed this is at least something
putting them you know I think a bit
behind but somewhat reasonable no I
could have been a ps4 controller no no
no you don't understand you can buy that
car from autonomous stuff and it comes
with an Xbox controller so I'm sure it
was an Xbox controller
um stop-and-go rav4 yeah well sorry
flashes yeah that's fine let's do that
oh all right let's go peace let's see
we'll do it a little more let's see what
else we can find this is mostly who we
wanted to make fun of today I have a map
I think if you really looked at this
frame for friend you could probably find
more dis engagements maybe free panda oh
oh it's wow you're here you reviewed the
whole drug did they disengage the
reporters in bachelor dances in the
channel right now Oh worried where
they're actually notice engagements what
what about what about that that thing
that I had that thing that I pointed out
okay well so the autonomous mode was
engaged the whole time so we've been in
cars where they say the word autonomous
the whole time but the safety driver did
corrections so we can engage the
autonomous mode the whole time and
adjust the steering wheel and that's not
considered a hard disengagement um it's
a little bit ballsy to not have the
brakes be considered a disengagement but
yeah I mean these are the these are the
numbers that I really want to get at
that's amazing
periscope I like this hey hey you know
what if it turns out that zukes is
awesome zooks is awesome um you will you
know you never saw their hands on the
wheel because they were in the backseat
what about the safety driver yeah so did
the safety driver make any Corrections
right all right all right I like this I
like I like this I like this integrity
and self-driving car journalism um yeah
so okay as far as investors going Zuke's
we can look into the details of their
round you never saw him touch her okay
cool
cool I take your word for it zooks
through without this engagement my good
physics um when the car pulled in front
it was weird did did they hit the brakes
is the question I mean I'd be interested
to see I thought for sure the human had
to take over okay
scared shit on that part they swore now
it's possible it was no like the car
clearly I hit the brakes too late but
they might have a decent you know
emergency braking thing I'm like uber oh
cool
no I'm glad you did um this is this is
excellent okay
this came for me let's back Suk's to a
do it okay all right we like Zeus yeah
why not talking about the exciting stuff
kama is doing instead of focusing on
competitors that's what we do in all the
other periscopes
[Music]
I will show you guys we do have so on
the highway merges
the one reporting was the worst of the
bunch yeah yeah I mean again I believe
that that was autonomous and somewhat
reasonable
we will talk right in front of we do
have a little poster where we celebrate
Zuke's this is why we don't build cars
yeah yeah but again that kind of stuff
is forgivable and I wouldn't call what
they did I'm safe I've seen I've seen
very conservative humans do the same
thing I didn't even call him out on that
it was that breaking event that was bad
but we won't come around on suits now if
I was ooks again I mean I guess this is
a way to differentiate yourself right I
guess that's really what it takes in the
market you don't think they have a
driver camera hey tzuke's
zooks release the driver camera video
from your drive with Ashley Babs do it
do it do it
no but seriously it was a time let's do
it we make a change in the world we're
demanding transparency and self-driving
car journalism and what do I make of way
mo in Arizona 11 douse key told me
there's no way to doing that for real
interesting um so here's the thing about
Wayne Wright way mo had that demo that
you saw in 2012 so what happened in the
last five years right way mo had a demo
where they could drive you back to the
Google office in 2012 what happened in
the last five years um I believe that so
okay
from what we can tell about lame-o they
are doing all of their stuff with a
safety driver the the way Mo's without
safety drivers are all done for PR so
there probably is a good chunk of these
engagements but do I believe that they
can launch in Chandler Arizona have you
seen I think I think if you look at
Chandler
I do kind of believe um is way mo AI a
joke no way mom as the most advanced
self-driving car in the world um what
the joke is where most PR it's way most
PR that that disgusts me honestly this
video doesn't disgust me I kind of like
it I think Suk's is overvalued but it's
good stuff right right it's a it's a
presentation of what it is and not what
is way No
right let's let's watch a hello I'm way
mo and oh no because yeah yeah why is
there no public photo because that's not
way mo doesn't do this it's it's this
kind of video
like vomited in my mouth no way Moe's
not driving public 2009 our team at
Google has been delving fully
self-driving technology
[Music]
now I'm driving in Austin Texas alright
um no no no no
so what way most says um and as far as I
can tell the early rider program does
exist uh unclear if these people are
paid actors or not I think the ones in
the videos are paid actors I do think
there are legitimate members of the
public in the early rider program I know
I know the video is disgusting but way
mo is not driving them without a safety
driver every single way mo out there in
the early rider program has somebody
behind the wheel of our self-driving
cars a few people who live near the area
have like looked around there and what
they can say is yeah there's a lot of
lame-o's driving around and they all
have people in the driver's seat oh the
people the people in the videos I really
think are actors one of these days maybe
we'll do a periscope breaking down when
we try to like crop out their face and
do a reverse image search for it and go
find their find their Instagram model
mayhem wherever actors are posting
themselves these days but yeah cool well
that got turned around we got we got we
got uh a props the valley actor for
coming into the periscope - uh do I have
a girlfriend now I have a company I
don't think the Tesla accident was
caused by Tesla's marketing I'm not
saying I like Zeus I'm not saying I like
zukes
all I'm saying is the valley hack came
in the channel who was in that car said
that he was watching there were not dis
engagements and I believed him so yeah
cool good for six but I would say I
would say if anybody out there from
Zuke's is watching I would love for you
to release just just the driver camera
of your driver driving throw it up on
YouTube technical crap it'll help you
with recruiting I mean cruise does it
right I like I like the videos that
Cruise released
yes Luke's is closed source I mean the
other thing too is like their sensors
are our generations behind windows right
what way mo would not have built their
own we got we got five million dollars
investment what would I do with five
hundred million dollars I have no idea
Marketing is autopilot I like Tesla's
marketing for the most part the truth
about the test the crashes is they don't
seem to be like statistically that rare
is closed source for pores okay so so
our now let's let's let's put our our
business hat and talk about Dukes for a
minute right so
zooks a1c bit of self-driving car
startup is closing a 500 million dollar
raised at a 300 billion dollar
post-money valuation prior to the deal
zooks valued at 2.7 billion interesting
so they actually raised it the same
amount of money I mean so so you can see
that like this is this so this is a
post-money valuation so the way a
post-money valuation works is you take
this and then you create 500 million
dollars worth of stock so everybody
everybody at Zuke's gotta get is called
dilution and also be curious to see if
we can find anything about the terms of
that investment who founded tzuke's oh
okay so here's the other thing that
kills me about tzuke's the symmetrical
cars no no no no I can't watch no no
more way no ads no okay we've all we've
all come around on jukes we've all come
around on Zuk Zuk says okay this is Tim
Kevin clay I was on a panel with him
once is just enough it soon
so no Carney mind we are we are fair and
open-minded here we are fair and
balanced periscope channel
these things though these things and the
idea of cars being symmetric to nice
manner they make fun of themselves
zooks has way becoming AI come as the
Apple one yeah I don't talk to any
engineer about bi-directional cars it
doesn't make sense to me a cars or cars
mostly move in one direction if you want
some video evidence of this look at how
much this car goes backwards as you see
all words pointing forwards here and not
backwards they want to be different with
the cars yeah I mean remember the time
we wanted to be different by making our
things bright green it was a dumb idea
2020 where it expects to put its first
vehicles on the road I mean making fun
of themselves like I like that alright
now we all like zooks now all right all
right all right all right Tommy I'm
marketing strategy revise you got a
marketing class we don't do any
marketing I just occasionally go on
periscope and make fun of people um
don't worry we make fun of ourselves too
it was media trolling yeah you say that
now we thought that people would love
the bright green new coke right
oh yeah I went sailing this weekend I
got sunburned
[Music]
celeb endow ski fix that way low stuff
is bullshit that's interesting what am I
making sir I liked it I mean it's good
I would not invest in zooks I would
really not invest in zooks
I don't see how they're ever gonna live
up to their their their their their
valuation I don't know like it's really
hard to tell the difference between hype
and not hype
I just remember I just remember how bad
the demos I did for you are like they
were so bad compared to what we have now
um reaching out to 11th St was good to
everybody should get levin dosti 's
comments on stuff i don't think making
the cars begins the differentiation i
met with them a few times he's a great
guy I'm like what's the best of luck bye
oh yeah
if we're doing the roundup of
self-driving car startups they have a
new logo now this is leopard on skis new
self-driving truck startup powered by
WordPress proudly no I don't think
Zuke's wants to sell you cars in one
syllable companies all right you have
changed my mind about zukes
when now Suk's fans without really
presumes to succeed we're not gonna make
fun of Zeus anymore and you know what
will really redeem Dukes is if they
release the video of the drive of the
safe to drive and not doing anything
then Zuke's will have a bill be golden
and worth their valuation all right guys
Wow so much can change in the span of 25
minutes
you know bro it up oh oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
in early 2015 zooks became firing staff
and retrofire housing prototyping
facility in a distressing sign for zooks
as early investors kevin lee clay also
spent $16,000 on a subzero office
refrigerator because he thought it
looked cool there's too much money in
Silicon Valley there's too much money
zooks
and its founders had a clear picture of
the vehicle they wanted it would have an
identical front and rear this is dumb
why this isn't how design works right
like you start with an engineering
requirement right there's a reason that
cars are asymmetrical like what you
think that all the other car
manufacturers are like shit we never
thought of that before right I really
don't understand what that buys were and
would be easy to service on the rare
occasion when it wore out its built-in
redundant cars right so this is an
interesting idea like car companies have
been in the service game for so long
especially when you look at Tesla right
successful services all their own cars
how does Luke's think that they can
possibly do better than Tesla on
servicing their cars okay zooks wants to
revolutionize 10 things and you know
what for most areas should go to
Mitsubishi 3000gt out of cars for real
steering
um but it's not about four-wheel
steering it's about why right like just
have a slip angle it's fine uh each
vehicle would have its own motors the
vehicle commit precise maneuvers and
tight spaces is that what most driving
us um can't anyone do better than Tesla
on serving their cars well I have a few
issues with Tesla's there are just rare
cars right so you can't really compare a
Model S to a Honda you have to compare a
Model S to a a car that sells similar
numbers they also the availability of
parts for a Tesla if you are not Tesla
is is rare but Tesla has an integrated
servicing solution
right and so I actually no I haven't
actually looked into the Consumer
Reports but all I'm saying is like if
you're designing from the perspective of
caring about keeping your service costs
low Tesla has the right incentives
whereas some other companies might not
right I mean does Volkswagen really care
if their cars break Kovu ii like the
Volkswagen dealerships want the
Volkswagen to bridge dealerships don't
make that much money selling new cars
they make money I'm bringing you in for
the service be every 18 months right so
Tesla at least if these cars are under
warranty actually wants to bring down
the true cost to repair so what I'm
saying is like that's the way they start
engineering whereas it's unclear to me
if putting redundancy in the car is a
good idea so for example um this is
something I talked about of an engineer
here a lot the body has redundancy at
the cellular level right a lot of the
things we are building too so like if
your body doesn't repair cells it just
kills the cell and makes a new one um
when you look at phones like this
beautiful car ie on right here by one
come to shop that time without a guy
coming by the ice glass shop you look at
the see on right here right if this
breaks you don't fix your eye on you go
to shop , da di you buy another eel all
right oh no user serviceable parts
inside right so if you were running a
fleet of cars that's the way you want to
deal with this right you don't really
want your cars to be like linking easy
to service because they're redundant
that doesn't make sense to me
Moe right so so what
why would eat wheel out its own motor
that makes no sense right and especially
when people start talking about putting
motors in the wheels I mean this looks
great from a design perspective but
you're putting way view you're putting
all this unsprung weight on the car
right you cannot gonna have a car that
that uh that that has a good suspension
an array of sensor to be seamlessly
integrated not jammed into an existing
vehicle have you seen the Tesla's they
look beautiful all right
the Tesla's with a b2 hardware look look
look beautiful
um though they should all have a dark
motor encounter you guys good no I feel
about that vaporwave worshiped Oh with
extreme precision did it turn through
those sideburns because it's impressive
from an engineering perspective it's
just questionable for me why perspective
why should we do we support the
Hollander SUV what if they doing torque
interceptors do we support the Hollander
I don't know Highliner no we don't
support the highlander we should should
i buy one of these so I could have a
zukes have my air at very own zukes
about the positions of all self-driving
cars and who do you want to talk about
uh no we don't have camera yeah we're
gonna merge it in soon there's a
highlighter not have let's see
Highlander Hybrid it says it has TSS P
Lane Departure alert I've never greater
cruise control know the Highlander
should be supported oh you worked
Annihilator port is it good
how come we haven't merchant it's closed
sorry cool so will support the zukes car
in a minute they can run they figure an
open pilot in their car um they're also
I mean you could just see this is little
things I actually I didn't show you guys
this but this is actually something that
shows you the car actually probably is
driving in autonomous mode Oh
just slide to book as ooks we don't know
any company in the world is driving that
multidimensional degree of difficulty
from urban the freeway to downtown
[Music]
delphi's doing it pretty well this will
be interesting is the app crazy or not
you know what make fun of this right
like I really shouldn't make fun of this
because what the app does for a lot of
people is complete some narrative right
if you're trying to tell a narrative
about how you're gonna sell your product
well that's kind of how you do it
what'll L compile up to 90 degree turns
I'm a little bit more excited about this
now you know apps can make a lot of
money it was exact
I don't be so add I mean it's not that
right like like like like like it's it's
not about it's not about it's not about
like like envy it's about hype killing
the industry it makes it difficult to
sell your driver assistance system which
is available for sale today at shop type
, today i Delphia is active when Ford is
promising you that by 2025 their
self-driving cars will take you to the
moon right like they won't but you see
the problem is when you're like look you
can do this thing it drives on the
highway it's pretty nice somebody comes
back and is like well but Ford's gonna
take me to the moon in 7 years
zooks can pivot to them all the
telehandlers oh ok alright don't get me
started on the telehandlers that's
that's a terrible idea
um yeah or they'll drive you to the moon
I think that's what they promise yeah
Delfy is named adaptive now Delfy
don't underestimate Delfy um as far as
as far as self-driving car companies
going you guys know that I've come
around on mobile I yeah sighs adjusting
fit I saw that movie right people will
install things themselves you gotta make
it a little easier but um look I mean
you could say the same thing about
furniture before IKEA right all people
will never build their own furniture
they do all right I'm gonna get up you
got a TaskRabbit to do it for try to be
Witter alright and I think I think we'll
leave it at that huge props to Ashley
Vance for coming and joining us in our
periscope follow her on twitter at
valley hack follow us on twitter at
comma a i make sure to buy things at
shop comedy i you'll have to ask zukes
that my money would be on less than us
but who knows man you can scale that up
with money I mean you want more driving
day to pay people to drive your your
virtual horseshit around all that that's
not street-legal yeah Turner Highlanders
around all day
[Music]
cool so yeah be winner no my issue is
not money but issue guys is technology
technology weak AI and the reason our
driver monitoring isn't better it's
pretty good but it would be better if
you guys would flip that little switch
on your camera that says front camera or
record and upload so if you're out there
and you have open pilot it's hugging the
left lane a lot you can go buy a zooks
they don't do that no I don't know
obviously don't know why that's
happening make sure on the latest
version oh oh lady on Oh Leon I don't
know anything about Leon's Aeon Gold
Edition uh if you think parents can use
commas now don't give him a comment yet
we're only halfway there that was the
press zero point five but it is for sale
today if you're an enthusiast when are
we going to Vegas can we'll do it we'll
do it I got something good planned you
know what I'm a fan of the zooks video a
fan of zooks I will I will let you know
when we have something cool we got to do
high key guys we got to do - demos the
hype is back self-driving cars are back
we're gonna win follow us on Twitter LED
night and the next hardball have LEDs
you know sup when can you buy any other
members on you can buy a pan on Amazon
come to a hype demo with a friend never
going to Def Con again and that's all of
that went which again are I gotta get
back on twitch guys alright thank you
all for watching this edition of suits
is not as bad as they thought we thought
they were and they're at least better
than juice arrow and they're way better
than theranos I put Fiji water now
that's a great investment
ok guys be a winner we'll leave it at
that buy my snow peas